It is important to remember that sometimes some customers take
需要注意的是 有些客户并不会这么快
a long time to convert from leads to paying customers.
从潜在客户转化为付费客户
Maybe they sign up or register for a free account for some months,
他们可能先注册了免费账户
and then they are prompted to become a paying customer.
过了几个月 才根据提示引导成为付费客户
In other words, your marketing campaign may take some time to
换言之 营销活动想要实现目标收入
realize the revenues it is trying to generate.
所需的时间可能较长
To come for that dealing in a lead conversion,
考虑到潜在客户转化过程中的这个因素
CAC is often calculated on the basis of your average sales cycle.
通常要基于平均销售周期来计算获取客户成本
Let's look at the following example.
看看以下例子
Here, we have a slightly different formula based on a 60-day average sales cycle.
现在我们要计算九月份的获取客户成本 但要基于 60 天的平均销售周期来算
We use the marketing cost for August,
我们要用到的数据包括 八月的营销成本…
and then use a ratio of the sales and marketing salaries,
…以及八月和九月的人员薪水总和的一半
and overhead costs, for the previous two months.
以及八月和九月的营业间接成本总和的一半
Don't get bogged down by the formula just yet.
先不要被公式难倒
Let's make sure we cover the concept first.
首先把这些概念理解透彻
So think of it as you're still paying for those costs,
不难理解 我们在等待营销成本获得回报、成功转化潜在客户的同时
the salaries, and the overhead cost,
我们也在持续支付人员薪水和营业间接成本
to realize the lead conversion which is the average cycle of two months in this example.
假设平均周期是两个月
So here's a formula. We take the marketing costs for August,
公式是这样的 我们取八月的营销成本
and we take half of the overhead cost with sales and marketing from August.
再取人员薪水和营业间接成本的总和的一半
So we add this amount,
所以 第一个数字
the marketing cost for August and add it to half.
是八月的营销成本 加上
So we multiply that with 0.5 of the overhead costs for August.
（人员薪水 + 营业间接成本）* 0.5
We add it to half of the overhead cost for September,
再加上 九月份的 （人员薪水 + 营业间接成本）* 0.5
because we're only taking into account the marketing cost for August and
因为我们只考虑八月份的营销成本
then averaging across the August and September overhead costs.
以及 八月份和九月份营业成本的平均值
I think it's done. So this is the numerator.
好了 这个就是分子了
The numerator is this,
分子就是这个
plus half of this,
加上这两个总和的 1/2
and half of this.That's the numerator,
以及这两个总和的 1/2 这就是分子
and what you're then doing is you're actually dividing it by
然后 将分子除以
the number of paid customers that you got in September.
九月份获得的付费客户
Because you're trying to gauge
因为我们要计算的是
what was the cost of acquiring these paid customers in September.
获得九月份的这些客户的成本是什么
If your sales cycle is two months,
如果销售周期是两个月
then you want to take the overhead costs for two months,
那么就像以上 我们用到了两个月的营业成本
so August and September, and average them,
八月和九月 然后取平均值
and that's what the 0.5 is doing,
也就是 乘以 0.5
and then you include the marketing cost.
然后再加上营销成本
This amount you spent on marketing to these paid customers back in August,
即 八月份的时候花在营销上的金额
and you divide it by the number of paid customers that you got in September.
然后 除以 九月份获得的付费客户
I've also included the formula here for you to see.
你可以看看这里的公式
So that's how you arrive at the CAC for the two month average cycle,
这就是如何计算销售周期为两个月的 CAC
and I copy the formula over to October as well.
把公式复制到十月份
[inaudible].
公式移到下面
So it's less confusing.
这样显得更清楚
So yes, you can see that the CAC is different
所以 可以看到 现在的 CAC
and lower than it was for the one-month cycle.
比销售周期为一个月的 CAC 要低
It was 148 and 138 before,
之前是 148 和 138
but now it's lower.
现在更低了
There's a reason for this.
这是有原因的
Previously, you were overestimating it.
之前 是过度估计了
You were hoping that the leads will convert to customers in a month.
你希望所有潜在客户都可以在 1 个月内就转化成付费客户
When in fact, it takes them two months.
而实际上 用了两个月
Businesses can decide their marketing campaign spending based on CAC.
业务决策者会根据 CAC 来决定营销投入
So for that reason, it is important to get more accurate estimate of CAC.
因此 计算准确的 CAC 非常重要